UA Presents Records 1991 - 2011
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- UA Presents Series Seasons Materials, 1995 - 2011; Series I
  - Estonian Philharmonic Chamber Choir, October 24, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Yamato, October 25, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 42nd Street, October 29, 2003 - November 12, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Astrid Hadad, November 1, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The Suzanna Farrell Ballet, November 4, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Wynton Marsalis, November 6, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Andre Watts, November 12, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Habib Koite and Bamada, November 18, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Ensemble Kaboul, November 18, 2003 – November 19, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Black Burlesque (revisted, November 22, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, December 6, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, December 16, 2003 – December 17, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Starlight Express, January 13, 2004 – January 18, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Movement (R)evolution: New African Dance, January 30, 2004 – January 31, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The Chieftains, February 2, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Paco de Lucia, February 3, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, February 5, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ilkhom Theatre of Uzbekistan, February 6, 2004 – February 7, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Preservation Hall Jazz Band, February 10, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Drepung Gomang Monks, February 10, 2004 – February 15, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Urinetown, February 13, 2004 – February 18, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Merce Cunningham Dance Company, February 14, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hall and Oates, February 15, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - R Carlos Nakai, February 17, 2004 – February 19, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Ronald K. Brown/Evidence, February 21, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, February 24, 2004 – February 29, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Riverdance, March 2, 2004 – March 7, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Newport Jazz Festival, March 9, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - The Spirit of Fes, March 11, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre, March 16, 2004 – March 17, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Batsheva Dance Company of Israel, March 24, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Kronos Quartet, March 26, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Mandy Patinkin, April 10, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - The Producers, May 24, 2004 – June 6, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Bobby McFerrin, September 10, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Lila Downs, October 1, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Miami City Ballet, October 8, 2004 – October 9, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Oliver!, October 12, 2004 – October 17, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Les Percussions de Guinee and Amazones, October 14, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Hairspray, October 26, 2004 – November 6, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - A Year with Frog and Toad, October 30, 2004 – October 31, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Bang on a Can All-Stars with Philip Glass, November 9, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - The English Concert, November 11, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Delfos Danza/Yjastras, November 19, 2004 – November 20, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Jose Feliciano, October 6, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Acoustic Africa, October 25, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - The English Concert, October 27, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Fred Garbo Inflatable Theater Co., October 29, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Maya Angelou, November 5, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mombasa Party/Sonny Rollins, November 15, 2006 – November 17, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dianne Reeves, December 2, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - The Chieftains, January 24, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Nai-Ni Chen Dance Company, March 11, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Cirque Dreams - Jungle Fantasy, April 21, 2007 – April 22, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Global Drum Project, September 20, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Dionne Warwick, October 5, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - The Brand New Kid, October 7, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company, October 16, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Ben Vereen, October 27, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Diavolo, November 2, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Perla Batalla and Charanga Cakewalk, November 4, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Herbie Hancock, November 14, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - A Christmas Carol, December 20, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Bravo Broadway, January 24, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Monterey Jazz Festival, January 26, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Les Ballets Trockadero de Monte Carlo, January 31, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Wynton Marsalis, February 1, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - St. Petersburg Ballet Theatre, February 9, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Leahy, February 10, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - In Perfect Harmony, February 16, 2008 – February 17, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Forever Tango, February 19, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Russian American Kids Circus, February 24, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, February 26, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Angelique Kidjo, March 8, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Czech Philharmonic Orchestra, March 8, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Ronald K. Brown/Evidence, March 11, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Mark Morris Dance Group, March 12, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - I Musici de Montreal, March 15, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Anoushka Shankar, March 28, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Eddie Palmier, April 2, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Parsons Dance, April 3, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Booker T and the MGs, April 15, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - B-52s, June 24, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Lily Tomlin, March 6, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Randy Travis, August 22, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Tap Dogs, August 26, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - The Ultimate Doo-Wop Show, October 3, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Laramie, October 12, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Kathy Mattea, November 7, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Ballroom With a Twist, November 14, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - The Fray, November 18, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Mannheim Steamroller, December 6, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - MOMIX, January 23, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - A Year With Frog and Toad, January 24, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Michael Feinstein, January 30, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Royal Winnipeg Ballet, February 6, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Universe of Dreams, February 12, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Olga Kerr, February 13, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - TAO: Martial Art of Drumming, February 20, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - The Music of Broadway, February 27, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Glenn Miller Orchestra, February 28, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Moscow State Radio Symphony Orchestra, March 8, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Ladysmith, March 14, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - The Vienna Boys Choir, March 20, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Ramsey Lewis and Patti Austin, March 26, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Guthries, April 9, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Aspen Sante Fe Ballet, April 16, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Monterey Jazz Festival, April 27, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Wicked, January 5, 2011 – January 23, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 117)
- UA Presents Organization Materials, 1991 - 2009; Series II
  Arranged alphabetically, this series contains articles pertaining to the organization of UA Presents such as its ticket sales and finances, articles on its former director, Ken Foster (1994 – 2003), as well as marketing materials showcasing the season as a whole.
  - Addy Awards Competition, February 24, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Arizona Daily Star articles and ads, 1991 – 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Daily Star articles and ads, 2000 – 2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Arizona Daily Star articles and ads, 2005 – 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arizona Daily Star articles and ads, 2007 – 2008 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Arizona Daily Wildcat articles and ads, 1998 – 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Arizona Daily Wildcat articles and ads, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Arizona Daily Wildcat articles and ads, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Arizona Daily Wildcat articles and ads, 2006 – 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Arizona Foothills Magazine articles and ads, November 2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Arizona Jewish Post articles and ads, October 13, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Artist Series at Centennial Hall, 1994 – 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Arts in Education, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bare Essential News for Kids articles and ads, 2006 – 2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - The Beethoven Quartet Cycle, 1999 – 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Caliente articles and ads, 1998 – 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Caliente articles and ads, 2005 – 2008 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Casino Del Sol, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Centennial Ghosts, 1998 – 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Centennial Hall, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Centennial Hall Photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Community Engagement, 2001 – 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - The DesertLeaf articles and ads, 2006 – 2008 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - The Explorer articles and ads, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Explorer articles and ads, 2007 – 2008 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Fall Season Announcement, 1998 – 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Fine Arts Institute, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - General Season Interest, 2001 – 2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - General UA Presents Photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Gold Star Gala, May 1, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Gold Star Gala, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Gold Star Gala, April 10, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gold Star Gala, December 5, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Governor’s Arts Award, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Green Valley News articles and ads, 2006 – 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hear’s Music 8th Anniversary Sale Catalog, November 1999 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hear’s Music 8th Anniversary Sale Catalog, November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Infinite Possibilities, 2000 - 2001 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Jazz Under the Stars, March 25, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Ken Foster, 1999 – 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Ken Foster resignation, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - La Estrella de Tucson articles and ads, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous articles and ads, 2008 – 2009 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Opening Season Publicity, 1995 – 1996 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Phantom of the Opera UA Presents News, 2001 – 2002 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Rio Nuevo, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - School Time Matinees, 1994 – 1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - School Time Matinees, 1998 – 2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Season Calendar, 2001 – 2002 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Season Clips, 1996 – 1997 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - South Tucson Norteno Festival and Street Fair, August 23, 2002 – August 24, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Spring Arts Preview, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Spring Preview, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Theater Season Programs, 1991 – 1995 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Tibet Week, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Tucson Arts Connection, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Tucson Citizen articles and ads, 2000 - 2004 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Tucson Citizen articles and ads, 2006 – 2007 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Tucson Citizen articles and ads, 2006 – 2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tucson Citizen articles and ads, 2008 - 2009 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tucson – City of the Arts, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tucson Lifestyle articles and ads, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tucson Lifestyle articles and ads, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Tucson Symphony Orchestra, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tucson Weekly articles and ads, 1998 – 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tucson Weekly articles and ads, 2005 – 2007 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - UA Artist Series – World of Arts, 1991 – 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - UA Presents (1 of 2), 1998 – 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - UA Presents (2 of 2), 1998 – 1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - UA Presents, 2007 – 2008 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - UA Presents, 2008 – 2009 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - UA Presents, 2009 – 2010 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - UA Presents, 2010 – 2011 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - UA Presents Broadway Series, 1999 – 2000 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - UA Presents Centennial Hall, 1996 – 1997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - UA Presents Centennial Hall Ticket Outlet, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - UA Presents Donation Form, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - UA Presents Donation History, 1993 – 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - UA Presents/Ken Foster, 2000 – 2005 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - UA Presents Media Alert, 1999 – 2000 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - UA Presents Media Highlights, 1996 – 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - UA Presents Memo, May 22, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - UA Presents News, 1997 - 2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - UA Presents News, 1999 - 2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - UA Presents News, 2000 – 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - UA Presents News, 2002 – 2003 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - UA Presents Press Coverage, 1996 – 1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - UA Presents Preview, 1996 – 1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - UA Presents Programs (1 of 3), 1999 – 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - UA Presents Programs (2 of 3), 1999 – 2000 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - UA Presents Programs (3 of 3), 1999 – 2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - UA Presents related articles, 2000 – 2001 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - UA Presents Season, 1995 – 1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - UA Presents Season, 1996 – 1997 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - UA Presents Season, 1997 – 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - UA Presents Season, 1999 – 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - UA Presents Season (1 of 2), 1999 – 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - UA Presents Season (2 of 2), 1999 – 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - UA Presents Season, 2002 - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - UA Presents Season, 2003 – 2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - UA Presents Season, 2004 – 2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - UA Presents Season Marketing, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - UA Presents Spring Shows, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - UA Presents Ticket Sales, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - UA Presents TTY, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - UA Presents various articles and ads, 1999 – 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Action Plans, 1999 – 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Evaluations, 1999 – 2005 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – General Policies, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Meetings, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Monthly Prospect Notes, 2002 – 2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - University of Arizona Foundation – Proposals, 1993 – 2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - US – Mexico Performing Arts Project Binational Database, May 30, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Various Publicity/Opening publications, 1996 – 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Winter Preview, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Artist and Theater Materials, 2000 - 2002; Series III
  The collection contains materials including programs, marketing information, flyers, and published articles on the organization itself, on its former director Ken Foster, on the series of events UA Presents has put on, as well as various artist and theater marketing materials.
  - Various Theater Season Programs, 1995 – 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Various Theater Season Programs, 1997 – 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Various Theater Season Programs, 1999 – 2000 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Various Theater Season Programs (1 of 2), 2000 – 2001 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Various Theater Season Programs (2 of 2), 2000 – 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Various Theater Season Programs, 2001 – 2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Ann Brown, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Artist Marketing Materials, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Artsventure, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Baaba Maal, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cedar Walton, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Columbia Artists Management, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Daniel Snyder Photographer Negatives, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - The Dirty Dozen Brass Band, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Disney’s Beauty and the Beast, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Ivan Lins, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Michael Stevens, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Nederlands Dans Theatre II “Skew Whiff”, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Omara, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Oumou, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Rinde Eckert, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Riverdance, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Tango Buenos Aires, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Tannis Gibson, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Terence Blanchard, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Vladimir Feltsman, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)